Miss.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
You're wearing such a thin dress.
What if you catch a cold?
Didn't Doctor Liu say
you shouldn't go out?
If something really happened to me,
that would be just what they want.
What are you talking about?
Prepare some things for me.
I'm going to put on a good show.
You already know the truth.
From now on,
what to do
is up to you.
Since you don't want to reveal your identity,
I won't ask too much.
But I have another request,
I hope you can agree.
Since you can find out
the relationship between Liu Taoy and Consort Ling,
I guess
you must be someone.
I'm in Prince Rui's Mansion now.
It's inconvenient to move.
I hope
you can help me check those medicines.
What are they for?
Is there a way to detoxify?
We've only met a few times.
Do you really trust me?
Yes.
[Why do I have a sense of familiarity]
[and trust towards him?]
It's not trust,
but exchange.
Since you're willing to help me like this,
I guess
I can still use you for something.
As long as I can save my family,
I'm willing to do anything.
Fine,
Then find a way
to locate the poison.
I can help you with that.
How do I reach you?
There's a cake vendor
at the western street corner.
A bamboo and wood wind chime
hangs in front of his stall,
with a red ribbon tied to it.
It can convey messages for you.
This
is your secret way of communicating.
You just told me like this.
Aren't you afraid...
Three days as the limit.
No waiting after that time.
It's a deal.
This favor,
you must remember it.
When I need you to repay,
I will ask for it.
Before that,
you'd better not die.
Imperial Physician Liu.
Why are you coming so late?
Go check on the princess consort.
What happened to her?
Since today,
she has been acting strangely,
as if she's a little foolish.
She doesn't even recognize me.
Foolish?
Let's go.
Go check on her.
Look,
she was fine a few days ago.
But today,
she's like a different person.
She doesn't recognize me,
and she doesn't even remember
Lady Shen's death.
This...
Princess Consort
doesn't like others to get close.
Be careful.
Okay.
Forgive me, Princess Consort.
Where do you feel uncomfortable?
Tell me.
I'll diagnose you.
Go away.
Go away, go away.
Go away, bad guy.
Imperial Physician Liu,
are you okay?
I told you.
Princess,
you forgot
I'm the physician who diagnoses you every day.
I'm not a bad guy.
I'll
diagnose you again.
Go.
Imperial Physician Liu,
are you okay?
Go.
Does Prince Rui
know about the situation of princess consort?
I haven't dared to report to Prince Rui.
The situation of princess consort is not optimistic.
Go and report to Prince Rui quickly.
Okay.
I'll go now.
Princess Consort,
don't be afraid.
I'll take you...
Go!
Go away!
Your Highness,
the shadow guard we placed in Prince Rui's Mansion
suddenly reported that
Princess Consort of Rui
seems to have
seems to have gone mad.
Could it be that she was traumatized
by Lady Shen's sudden death?
Gone mad?
Such useless fools!
Can't even take care of their own master!
Princess Consort was fine yesterday.
I don't know
what happened.
Your ears are so pretty!
Can you give them to me?
Cut them off and give them to me.
Princess Consort, please spare me.
-Give them to me. -Stop.
My dear.
This bad guy bullies me.
Can you drive him out?
Imperial Physician Liu.
She is...
You go to treat your wound first.
Yes.
You
just called me husband.
Do you remember who you are?
Of course I do.
I'm Princess Consort of Rui.
Then my husband is Prince Rui.
That bad guy
called you Prince Rui.
What?
You're not my husband?
Of course I'm your husband.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
No one dares to bully you.
Shen Suhe.
Stop pretending.
Let go of him.
Who are you?
Don't think you can get away with this
by pretending to be crazy.
I'll see how long you can keep this up.
Chuchu.
Stop.
Your Highness.
Can't you see
this bitch is just pretending?
Honey.
Who is this bad woman?
Why don't you kick her out?
She...
What's wrong?
Are you afraid of this bad woman?
I tell you,
my father is the Prime Minister of the current dynasty.
I know the Emperor.
If you don't drive her out,
we'll go to the Emperor
and ask him to drive her out.
You...
She is a new maid of mine.
She's not a bad woman.
Maid?
If she is a maid,
can she wash my feet?
I'll send other maids to serve you, okay?
No.
I want her to do it.
You...
Princess consort,
you should wash carefully.
Otherwise,
you'll be hungry tonight.
Hungry?
I don't want to be hungry.
I'll wash them carefully.
Carefully.
You hurt me.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, let me blow on it.
Get away!
You useless girl!
Hurry up!
One more.
Put it in for me.
Move!
You...
Why don't you wash it?
Be gentle.
Or my husband will scold you.
Wash it!
What are you waiting for?
Ouch!
Why don't you wash it?
You're so annoying!
It hurts so much.
Shen Suhe.
[Shen Suhe has become crazy lately.]
[Could it be]
[that the drug has been successfully developed?]
When I
tested the drug on the madam,
I used too much,
which caused her death.
So I reduced the dosage
for the princess consort.
But in just two or three days,
the princess consort fell ill.
This is indeed a bit too fast.
Could it be
that she is pretending to be mad?
I have taken the princess consort's pulse.
She is indeed poisoned.
As for whether it is caused by taro powder,
I
can't make a conclusion for the time being.
These days,
observe her carefully.
If she's truly mad, fine.
But if she's faking it,
I'll make her pay for Lady Shen's death.
Zhiyan,
did you hear that?
You were right.
His Highness
is indeed behind her death.
But
how did you know
the poison
would destroy one's mind?
I wasn't sure either,
so I just wanted to test it.
But Mu Jinghao's reaction just now
confirmed the effect of the poison.
That's why I took the opportunity
to humiliate Ling Chuchu.
It seems that
I became foolish in my dreams,
also because of Mu Jinghao.
Your acting just now
almost made me believe it.
But thinking of Ling Chuchu
being angry
and helpless,
it's really satisfying.
But Miss,
since you know Prince Rui
colluded with Dr. Liu to harm you,
why don't you tell Master?
If he knows,
he would have reported
to the Emperor.
The evidence we have now
is not enough to prove that Mu Jinghao did it.
He can easily shift all the blame
onto Dr. Liu.
At that time,
it will be even harder for us
to catch him.
That's true.
What should we do next?
Where are the things I asked you to hide?
Go away.
Go away, bad guy.
Imperial Physician Liu,
are you okay?
This...
Princess,
do you remember?
I'm the Imperial Physician Liu who checks your pulse every day.
Miss.
Zhiyan.
I'm going out tonight.
You watch the door.
Don't let anyone find out.
Miss.
You're leaving me alone again.
Don't worry.
I'll be back as soon as possible.
Your Highness.
Have you found General Xiao?
The shadow guard spotted him
near the outskirts.
However,
there seems to be another group looking for him.
We're not sure of their identities yet.
Regardless,
we must find Xiao Wei first.
Yes.
Let's go.
My lady,
please stop washing.
Your hands are all red.
His Highness will be worried
if he sees this.
His heart
must have been taken by that bitch.
He won't care about me anymore.
Who else
can take my heart but you?
Your Highness.
You can leave now.
Chuchu,
why are you so hot-tempered?
Even if you don't cherish your body,
I will be heartbroken.
Are you falling in love with Shen Suhe?
She is not as good as you.
How could I fall in love with her?
Then why do you always help her bully me?
She is the daughter of the Prime Minister.
If she reports me
to my father,
It's not good for me.
Chuchu,
just bear with it for a while.
I promise you,
in less than a month,
Shen Suhe
and the entire Prime Minister's Residence
will have no chance to turn things around.
Take people to find Xiao Wei.
Your Highness,
I'll stay here to deal with them.
No more talk!
Go!
Split up!
Find General Xiao!
Use the whistle as a signal!
Yes, sir!
[It's been hours.]
[It's just]
[a chance encounter.]
[I was too naive.]
Sorry to
for keeping you waiting.
I thought
you wouldn't wait for me.
I believe
you're a man of your word.
Do you always trust people so easily?
But this time, I trusted the right person,
didn't I?
This...
You're injured.
You're in trouble yourself.
You'd better take care of yourself.
It's almost dawn.
You should go back to your mansion.
I'll tell you
if there's any new clue.
Young Master Lou,
you should be careful, too.
Don't die before me.
Don't worry.
I'll be around
to collect my debt from you.
That would be best.
Farewell.
What's wrong?
Speak!
Where exactly is Xiao Wei hiding?
I'd like to see
how long you can keep this up.
Your Highness,
you don't need to go to great lengths
to find General Xiao.
He can show up himself.
You have a good idea?
If the news of General Xiao's
treachery is spread in the capital,
he will definitely show up
to prove his innocence.
As a general who has won many battles,
he suddenly lost the battle
and returned to the capital overnight.
What would His Majesty think?
Besides,
we've already received
the secret letter about his treason.
We'll have one of his subordinates
come forward and expose him.
In that case,
what would Your Majesty decide?
The letter only vaguely mentioned the PM.
Even if the Emperor punishes Xiao Wei,
it won't affect him.
To control him,
we failed to develop taro powder,
but now his daughter
obeys you.
Xiao Wei and Prime Minister Shen are old friends.
If General Xiao is in trouble,
Shen wouldn't stand by.
At that time,
you can stir up trouble,
and Your Majesty will be suspicious of him.
Fifteenth,
you're a good strategist.
I'll do as you said.
Yes.
Sister,
what happened?
Who is this man?
Thank you for letting me in tonight.
He saved my life.
I must repay this favor.
Please don't tell
Father about this.
I can keep your secret.
But you should tell me
what happened.
I wanted to
visit you at the mansion.
But
I was told that you were sick
and couldn't see me.
I was kicked out.
Sister,
tell me the truth.
Did he bully you?
No.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
But there are some things
I can't tell you and father yet.
I'll explain everything
to you later.
Who's there?
My lord.
I thought there was a burglar in the house.
I'm here to find something in my sister's room.
It's okay now.
You can go back to rest.
Yes.